[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Do you remember bumping me for Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "bumping", "me", "for", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I'm a British gentleman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "British", "gentleman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "If you could relive five minutes of your life, which would they be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "relive", "five", "minutes", "of", "your", "life", ",", "which", "would", "they", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "I thought about that, because I thought you might ask me that, because I think it's a really good question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "about", "that", ",", "because", "I", "thought", "you", "might", "ask", "me", "that", ",", "because", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "really", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "So let's start by letting everybody know how this show came to be because initially, you weren't supposed to be a live breaking news show, correct?", "question_tokens": ["So", "let", "'s", "start", "by", "letting", "everybody", "know", "how", "this", "show", "came", "to", "be", "because", "initially", ",", "you", "were", "n't", "supposed", "to", "be", "a", "live", "breaking", "news", "show", ",", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, initially, the idea was -- I'd do a show back in the UK called \"Life Stories,\" which is a more auto-biographical hour- long interview with one guest.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "initially", ",", "the", "idea", "was", "--", "I", "'d", "do", "a", "show", "back", "in", "the", "UK", "called", "``", "Life", "Stories", ",", "''", "which", "is", "a", "more", "auto-biographical", "hour-", "long", "interview", "with", "one", "guest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Are you sure you didn't invite yourself to be on Oprah's show?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sure", "you", "did", "n't", "invite", "yourself", "to", "be", "on", "Oprah", "'s", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, I was desperate and she listened to this desperate pathetic little Brit, and thought come, come to Chicago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "desperate", "and", "she", "listened", "to", "this", "desperate", "pathetic", "little", "Brit", ",", "and", "thought", "come", ",", "come", "to", "Chicago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oprah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How did you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, look, I mean -- I have spent my life back in Britain as a journalist involved with breaking news.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "have", "spent", "my", "life", "back", "in", "Britain", "as", "a", "journalist", "involved", "with", "breaking", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Did you watch your own interviews?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "watch", "your", "own", "interviews", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What is your nightmare scenario for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "nightmare", "scenario", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "We don't want to see this stark Mediavalism that represses women, that crushes the rights of people, that rolls us back a millennium, that fosters violence and does everything that we abhor that it would take over.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "see", "this", "stark", "Mediavalism", "that", "represses", "women", ",", "that", "crushes", "the", "rights", "of", "people", ",", "that", "rolls", "us", "back", "a", "millennium", ",", "that", "fosters", "violence", "and", "does", "everything", "that", "we", "abhor", "that", "it", "would", "take", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "OK, and what did you think of your performance?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "and", "what", "did", "you", "think", "of", "your", "performance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "I found him incredibly impressive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "him", "incredibly", "impressive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Did you like him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "like", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I did like him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "like", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What about Colin Powell?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Colin", "Powell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Colin Powell is a remarkable man.", "answer_tokens": ["Colin", "Powell", "is", "a", "remarkable", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "You don't know what gumbo is?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "gumbo", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, I do now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Why can't it be my thing, too?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "it", "be", "my", "thing", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, it is your thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "your", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "How do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "-- seems a little shallow to me.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "seems", "a", "little", "shallow", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "So where would you like to begin?", "question_tokens": ["So", "where", "would", "you", "like", "to", "begin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Some of them were impressive people I've met actually turned out not to run for president which I thought was a shame.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "of", "them", "were", "impressive", "people", "I", "'ve", "met", "actually", "turned", "out", "not", "to", "run", "for", "president", "which", "I", "thought", "was", "a", "shame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Are you a fan?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Has he disappointed, you Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "disappointed", ",", "you", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "disappointed", "that", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "more", "bold", "decisions", "from", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "How's he doing, the half white guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "he", "doing", ",", "the", "half", "white", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I'm still rooting for the black president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "still", "rooting", "for", "the", "black", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "That is a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Why shouldn't I ask Heidi Klum?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "n't", "I", "ask", "Heidi", "Klum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "She's German and a supermodel.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "German", "and", "a", "supermodel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Well, are you American yet?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "are", "you", "American", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 238, "question": "But she's an American citizen, why shouldn't I ask her?", "question_tokens": ["But", "she", "'s", "an", "American", "citizen", ",", "why", "should", "n't", "I", "ask", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, I guess you could ask her but it just seems like an odd choice to ask somebody --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "you", "could", "ask", "her", "but", "it", "just", "seems", "like", "an", "odd", "choice", "to", "ask", "somebody", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "When you were covering the royal wedding, how painful was it to sit next to Anderson Cooper for that many hours?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "covering", "the", "royal", "wedding", ",", "how", "painful", "was", "it", "to", "sit", "next", "to", "Anderson", "Cooper", "for", "that", "many", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "ORGAN: It was a joy for Anderson.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "It", "was", "a", "joy", "for", "Anderson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson Cooper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Am I now doing the Tebow?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "now", "doing", "the", "Tebow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "You are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"], "LOCATION": ["William"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Now have you had them on the show yet?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "have", "you", "had", "them", "on", "the", "show", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I haven't yet but the invitation remains extended to William and Kate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "yet", "but", "the", "invitation", "remains", "extended", "to", "William", "and", "Kate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Kim was on the show?", "question_tokens": ["Kim", "was", "on", "the", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, actually it was a week before we taped it because it coincided with her book launch.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", "it", "was", "a", "week", "before", "we", "taped", "it", "because", "it", "coincided", "with", "her", "book", "launch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "So does that kind of thing piss you off?", "question_tokens": ["So", "does", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "piss", "you", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Your second?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "My last.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "last", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Are you auditioning?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "auditioning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Are we done?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Are you under the influence right now of any substances?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "under", "the", "influence", "right", "now", "of", "any", "substances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do you remember bumping me for Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "bumping", "me", "for", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "So why were you so nice to him?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "were", "you", "so", "nice", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I like Charlie Sheen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "Charlie", "Sheen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Do you think he was high, though, while you were interviewing him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "was", "high", ",", "though", ",", "while", "you", "were", "interviewing", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What is this problem here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "this", "problem", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I think you're absolutely right on that -- on that point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "absolutely", "right", "on", "that", "--", "on", "that", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 447, "question": "You're in the 1 percent, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "in", "the", "1", "percent", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Well, I'm not in the 1 percent, no, but I am --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "the", "1", "percent", ",", "no", ",", "but", "I", "am", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you know the answers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "answers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "What are you worth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "How?", "question_tokens": ["How", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Just, they can.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", ",", "they", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How do you think Larry King would have handled the situation, like any of those?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "Larry", "King", "would", "have", "handled", "the", "situation", ",", "like", "any", "of", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "In the graceful, brilliant way he did with every situation for 25 years, one of my heroes.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "graceful", ",", "brilliant", "way", "he", "did", "with", "every", "situation", "for", "25", "years", ",", "one", "of", "my", "heroes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry King"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Is he one of your heroes?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "one", "of", "your", "heroes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Yes, he genuinely was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "genuinely", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "How do you feel when you have to interview somebody like that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "have", "to", "interview", "somebody", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It's always challenging.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "always", "challenging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Do you think Barbara Walters is feisty?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "Barbara", "Walters", "is", "feisty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "My God.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara Walters"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Oh, you did not -- I'll throw this mic pack at your --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "did", "not", "--", "I", "'ll", "throw", "this", "mic", "pack", "at", "your", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Once, and I remain there.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", ",", "and", "I", "remain", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Not bad, was it?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "bad", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "No, you had Oprah.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "had", "Oprah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Was she your most impressive guest that you have had?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "your", "most", "impressive", "guest", "that", "you", "have", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP$", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Certainly one of them, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "one", "of", "them", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Probably the biggest, right?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "biggest", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "So, how many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "how", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you talk about that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "talk", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I have been known to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "been", "known", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 608, "question": "And your previous wife?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "previous", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "That would also be an --", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "also", "be", "an", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How many others were there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "others", "were", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "If you could relive five minute of your life, which would they be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "relive", "five", "minute", "of", "your", "life", ",", "which", "would", "they", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I thought about that because I thought you might ask me that, because I think it's a really good question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "about", "that", "because", "I", "thought", "you", "might", "ask", "me", "that", ",", "because", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "really", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "See how easy it is?", "question_tokens": ["See", "how", "easy", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "So what would you want to relive from that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "would", "you", "want", "to", "relive", "from", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I would relive the moment they announced that we won newspaper of the year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "relive", "the", "moment", "they", "announced", "that", "we", "won", "newspaper", "of", "the", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Because it was long-winded and you really didn't say much.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "was", "long-winded", "and", "you", "really", "did", "n't", "say", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "If you could walk through that door again, would you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "walk", "through", "that", "door", "again", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes, I absolutely agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "absolutely", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "What can I say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "I", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "We're going to get into that when we come back.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "into", "that", "when", "we", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Does sex get better with age, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "sex", "get", "better", "with", "age", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "You tell us.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "tell", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "question_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "where", "do", "we", "go", "from", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "hoping", "somewhere", "nice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "So what's that about?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "that", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "It's about good interview technique.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "good", "interview", "technique", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "I liked him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "liked", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Females or male comedians?", "question_tokens": ["Females", "or", "male", "comedians", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "A lot of comedians are quite depressive, tricky characters.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "comedians", "are", "quite", "depressive", ",", "tricky", "characters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "What about Kathy Griffin, when she crawled over the desk and tried to face hump you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Kathy", "Griffin", ",", "when", "she", "crawled", "over", "the", "desk", "and", "tried", "to", "face", "hump", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Well a completely mad woman doing a completely mad thing on live television, and one of the most dangerous moments of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "a", "completely", "mad", "woman", "doing", "a", "completely", "mad", "thing", "on", "live", "television", ",", "and", "one", "of", "the", "most", "dangerous", "moments", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy Griffin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Can you imagine sitting here and Kathy Griffin comes at you like a rampant hyena?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "sitting", "here", "and", "Kathy", "Griffin", "comes", "at", "you", "like", "a", "rampant", "hyena", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "No, I can't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy Griffin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "How did you defend yourself?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "defend", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "It was -- I had to fend her off, like I did you.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "I", "had", "to", "fend", "her", "off", ",", "like", "I", "did", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Can we expect the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "expect", "the", "little", "patter", "of", "little", "Beyonce", "and", "Jay-Zs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "You know, only God knows.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "only", "God", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "Would you mind asking him to tell me?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "mind", "asking", "him", "to", "tell", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "When did you join, first of all?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "join", ",", "first", "of", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "I don't remember when I joined.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "remember", "when", "I", "joined", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 798, "question": "How long have you bee on?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "you", "bee", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 799, "answer": "One year.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "Have you reached out to him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "reached", "out", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "No, but I keep saying on the show, hoping that he's sitting there watching, thinking to himself, if I just do one interview with one guy on TV, it's going to be this guy.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "keep", "saying", "on", "the", "show", ",", "hoping", "that", "he", "'s", "sitting", "there", "watching", ",", "thinking", "to", "himself", ",", "if", "I", "just", "do", "one", "interview", "with", "one", "guy", "on", "TV", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "this", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "What do you have to offer him that everybody else doesn't?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "have", "to", "offer", "him", "that", "everybody", "else", "does", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "I do interviews in a different way than anyone else.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "interviews", "in", "a", "different", "way", "than", "anyone", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "What if he doesn't like it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "like", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "You obviously love it, because you keep coming back.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "obviously", "love", "it", ",", "because", "you", "keep", "coming", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "What if he doesn't like it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "like", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "He will like it, because he's my hero.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "will", "like", "it", ",", "because", "he", "'s", "my", "hero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "Is that the life you wish you could lead?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "life", "you", "wish", "you", "could", "lead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "What he your idea of a little bit of heaven?", "question_tokens": ["What", "he", "your", "idea", "of", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "heaven", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Being here with you, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "here", "with", "you", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 861, "question": "What's the big dream role for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "big", "dream", "role", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "To play you.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "play", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]